const qBank = [
  {
    question:
      "Who is the Owner of this Website ?",
    answers: ["Alok", "Raja", "Lipsa", "Anita"],
    correct: "Anita",
    questionId: "099099"
  },
  {
    question:"How is the best partner of Raja Sahoo ?",
    answers: ["Josna", "Lipsa", "Anita", "Ex"],
    correct: "Anita",
    questionId: "183452"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Company Raja Sahoo Working on ?",
    answers: ["Qwop", "Isha", "Shopweb", "WFH"],
    correct: "Isha",
    questionId: "267908"
  },
  {
    question: "What's the best voice call partner ?",
    answers: [
      "Sagar",
      "Anita",
      "Jhoney",
      "Josna"
    ],
    correct: "Sagar",
    questionId: "333247"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the most common factor of QWOP team ?",
    answers: ["R&D on Master", "GD on eX", "GOA plan", "get Together"],
    correct: "GD on eX",
    questionId: "496293"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was the PHP developer at QWOP?",
    answers: [
      "Sankhi",
      "Avhilash",
      "Sagar",
      "Namrata"
    ],
    correct: "Avhilash",
    questionId: "588909"
  },
  {
    question:
      'Who is the owner of  PKS Technolgy?',
    answers: ["Rajani", "Alok", "Pramod", "Sagar"],
    correct: "Pramod",
    questionId: "648452"
  },
  {
    question: "QWOP Technology belongs from where?",
    answers: ["BBSR", "Nayagrh", "USA", "NO place"],
    correct: "No Place",
    questionId: "786649"
  },
  {
    question:
      "PKS Technology is working where?",
    answers: ["USA", "UAE", "BBSR", "NO where"],
    correct: "No where",
    questionId: "839754"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which one is best client to Qwop?",
    answers: [
      "BCCST",
      "Ganes Ppr",
      "Elite",
      "NO one"
    ],
    correct: "No one",
    questionId: "98390"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the best Employe and Partner to Pramod Master?",
    answers: ["Rajani", "Alok", "Abhilash", "Sagar"],
    correct: "Sagar",
    questionId: "1071006"
  },
  {
    question: "What Master says most?",
    answers: ["Ground", "notePen", "LetMeCalU", "ArjunBabu"],
    correct: "ArjunBabu",
    questionId: "1174154"
  },
  {
    question: "SHOPWEB is situated at where?",
    answers: ["CTC", "BBSR", "RKL", "UP"],
    correct: "BBSR",
    questionId: "1226535"
  },
  {
    question: "who writes that application to master?",
    answers: ["Sagar", " Abhilash", "Raja", "Gudu"],
    correct: "Abhi",
    questionId: "1310938"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the largest organ of the human body?",
    answers: ["Skin", "Heart", "large Intestine", "Liver"],
    correct: "Skin",
    questionId: "1436873"
  },
  {
    question: "Which sign of the zodiac is represented by the Crab?",
    answers: ["Cancer", "Libra", "Virgo", "Sagittarius"],
    correct: "Cancer",
    questionId: "1515110"
  },
  {
    question: "What was the salary of Sagar Sahu in QWOP ?",
    answers: ["8k", "12k", "15k", "10k"],
    correct: "15k",
    questionId: "1642728"
  },
  {
    question:
      "What does the 'S' stand for in the abbreviation SIM, as in SIM card? ",
    answers: ["Subscriber", "Single", "Secure", "Solid"],
    correct: "Subscriber",
    questionId: "1747256"
  },
  {
    question:
      "who cheated most in QWOP & PKS ?",
    answers: ["Abhi", "Raja", "Master", "Sagar"],
    correct: "Master",
    questionId: "1822532"
  },
  {
    question: "what salary master gives to Namrata?",
    answers: [
      "15k",
      "18k",
      "confidential",
      "More & More"
    ],
    correct: "confidential",
    questionId: "195075"
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the designation of Raja sahoo?',
    answers: ["UI", "Frontend", "web developer", "All"],
    correct: "All",
    questionId: "2019778"
  },
  {
    question: "Why i left SHOPWEB?",
    answers: ["future", "money", "fight", "Due Date"],
    correct: "Money",
    questionId: "2134343"
  },
  {
    question: "How old i am ?",
    answers: [
      "26",
      "24",
      "25",
      "27"
    ],
    correct: "26",
    questionId: "2210799"
  },
  {
    question:
      "who loves me more in Qwop ?",
    answers: ["Master", "Namrata", "ArjunBabu", "No ONe"],
    correct: "No One",
    questionId: "2379831"
  },
  {
    question: "WHat is the designation of Sagar?",
    answers: ["SEO sp", "BDM SP", "Allrounder", "Assistans"],
    correct: "Assistans",
    questionId: "2426418"
  },
  {
    question: "Who did interview Sankhalika ?",
    answers: ["Sagar", "Abhilash", "Master", "Namrata"],
    correct: "Abhilash",
    questionId: "2510086"
  },
  {
    question: "Lipsa working on what?",
    answers: [
      "PHP",
      "Designer",
      "wordpress",
      "All"
    ],
    correct: "All",
    questionId: "2685745"
  },
  {
    question:
      "who's friend Josna ?",
    answers: ["lipsa", "Raja", "Altab", "All"],
    correct: "All",
    questionId: "2796884"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these colours is NOT featured in the logo for Google?",
    answers: ["Pink", "Yellow", "Blue", "Green"],
    correct: "Pink",
    questionId: "2838900"
  },
  {
    question: 'Who did xerox of : Jorse Bolo Master Bou _?',
    answers: ["Abhilash", "Sagar", "Gudu", "Johney"],
    correct: "Sagar",
    questionId: "298060"
  },
  {
    question: "How many Interns Joined in QWOP ?",
    answers: ["4", "3", "2", "5"],
    correct: "5",
    questionId: "3096579"
  },
  {
    question: "Who's fried is Jhoney Sins?",
    answers: [
      "Sagar",
      "Abhilash",
      "Raja",
      "Partha"
    ],
    correct: "Raja",
    questionId: "3182461"
  },
  {
    question: "What do the letters in the GMT time zone stand for?",
    answers: [
      "Greenwich Mean Time",
      "Global Meridian Time",
      "General Median Time",
      "Glasgow Man Time"
    ],
    correct: "Greenwich Mean Time",
    questionId: "3239112"
  },
  {
    question: "Now where is Master ?",
    answers: ["USA", "Nayagarh", "BBSR", "On meeting"],
    correct: "On meeting",
    questionId: "3318503"
  },
  {
    question:
      'What master is wearing most, now a days ?',
    answers: ["Jogers", "Bermunda", "Hot PAnt", "Boxer"],
    correct: "Boxer",
    questionId: "3410327"
  },
  {
    question: "on what company Abhilash Working?",
    answers: ["morkalix", "Reaxie", "OCCAC", "No JOb"],
    correct: "No Job",
    questionId: "3542596"
  },
  {
    question: "Where is dipita working now ?",
    answers: ["BBSR", "Banglore", "Kolkata", "WFH"],
    correct: "WFH",
    questionId: "3667517"
  },
  {
    question: "What do the letters of the fast food chain KFC stand for?",
    answers: [
      "Kentucky Fried Chicken",
      "Kentucky Fresh Cheese",
      "Kibbled Freaky Cow",
      "Kiwi Food Cut"
    ],
    correct: "Kentucky Fried Chicken",
    questionId: "3791672"
  },
  {
    question: "Vhabani Is working on what ?",
    answers: ["reactJs", "HTML", "ReactNative", "NodeJs"],
    correct: "ReactNative",
    questionId: "3893585"
  },
  {
    question: 'AltabRaja Is what kind of developer',
    answers: ["REact", "PHP", "Laravel", "All"],
    correct: "Green",
    questionId: "3913430"
  },
  {
    question: "How tall is the Burj Khalifa?",
    answers: ["2,722 ft", "2,717 ft", "2,546 ft", "3,024 ft"],
    correct: "2,722 ft",
    questionId: "4049121"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following  games we played with sankhalika?",
    answers: ["ludo", "Antakhyari", "Para odu", "statue"],
    correct: "Antakhyari",
    questionId: "4150746"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Anita Behera is working on What ?",
    answers: ["PHP", "Wordpress", "HTML", "Graphic", "all"],
    correct: "All",
    questionId: "4235063"
  },
  {
    question: "Which sign of the zodiac comes between Virgo and Scorpio?",
    answers: ["Libra", "Gemini", "Taurus", "Capricorn"],
    correct: "Libra",
    questionId: "4321002"
  },
  {
    question: "Who's outgoing spent much with Raja Sahoo",
    answers: [
      "Jhoney",
      "Partha",
      "Vhabani",
      "Sagar"
    ],
    correct: "Sagar",
    questionId: "4442286"
  },
  {
    question: "Where is parth Sarathi Das Now ?",
    answers: [
      "Banglore",
      "Baleswar",
      "BBSR",
      "Hydrabad"
    ],
    correct: "Baleswar",
    questionId: "4564430"
  },
  {
    question: "What company developed ReactJS?",
    answers: ["Google", "Facebook", "MIcrosoft", "Apple"],
    correct: "Facebook",
    questionId: "4630606"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which country facing Inside War now a days",
    answers: ["Pakistan", "China", "Afganistan", "USA"],
    correct: "Afganistan",
    questionId: "4795960"
  },
  {
    question: "Which cricket player is mentor now?",
    answers: ["Kohili", "Dhoni", "Rhoit", "Raina"],
    correct: "Dhoni",
    questionId: "4811162"
  },
  {
    question: "When Raja Sahoo will do the marriage ?",
    answers: ["December", "January", "March", "NOt Soon"],
    correct: "NOt Soon",
    questionId: "4982981"
  }
];


export default(n = 5) =>
  Promise.resolve(qBank.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));
 
  // const qBank